If you have a kessia, wear it.
So I went to the mall yesterday and I live in a neighborhood that has a large Zionist community.
And I wore mine proudly to the mall knowing somebody could sneer at me.
You know, somebody might say something off the side of their neck.
More bold, somebody might try to star something.
Mama say, mama say, mama say, mama go say.
So I was ready.
You know what I got instead?
I got love.
I had three different people stop me and say, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you for wearing your kessia.
It was a younger woman, a man.
He stopped and gave me a dap.
And an older woman gave me a thumbs up.
She said, I see this.
I see this.
Thank you. Thank you.
So we must always represent for the community that we support.
Even when we feel like we're the lone soldier in the situation.
And when we see somebody else representing, we must always acknowledge them.
So we can always know where we are and who we're with.